

Bath, BA2 9HP +44(0)7731 659 516 tomrickhuss@gmail.com

BIOGRAPHY

6+ years industry experience, client & agency side, working across both the public & private sectors for organisations of all shapes and sizes. A versatile strategist with brand, creative, comms and digital (web / app, social & CRM) experience. And an appetite to keep up with the latest 'goings-on' — news, tech, trends etc.



/tomrickhuss

in

/in/tomrickhuss

EXPERIENCE

STRATEGIST (MW > SNR)

Mr B & Friends | Mar 2019 - Mar 2021

Accounts included: Accoya (Dutch wood), Verne Global (Icelandic data centre), Regina (Ioo roll), TLT (law firm)

STRATEGIST (JNR > MW)

Great State | May 2016 - Feb 2019

Accounts included: Arthritis Research UK, Bristol Airport,
Orange, The Royal Navy, UNHCR (UN refugee agency)

CREATIVE

buffalozoo | Oct 2015 - Mar 2016

Accounts included: Bristol Airport, Direct Line Group, Heathrow Airport, National Trust, Three

QUALIFICATIONS

ADVERTISING WITH MARCOMMS

Bournemouth University | 2011 - 2015

1st. 'Best Overall Paper' for dissertation. Published in academic journal twice. Account planner of the year

A LEVELS & GCSES

Kingdown School | 2004 - 2011

Maths — A, Psychology — A, Biology — C 5 A*s (equivalent), 4 As and 2 Bs

MISC.

The School of Life | 1993 - Present

Abstained from coffee for 365 days in 2018. MTB chariot racing world champion. Author of Furlough Diaries.

INTERESTS



I'm also interested in exploring new places and experiencing new cultures (see map >)



TESTIMONIALS

Matt Boffey | MD, London Strategy Unit "Not afraid of a blank piece of paper"

Ben Kay | Planning Director, WPP
"Equal amounts of diligence, commitment,
intelligence and good humour"

SKILLS

Research
Literal thinking
Lateral thinking
Problem-solving
Communication

